and i think those are the things one can already see barring a severe depression in which economics
of necessity become more important uh economics for the determining buying class which is 70
percent maybe of every spring and they can make choices and so is it you know here are those
young people and a lot of them who buy that beautiful house and then for four
years maybe they don't sleep in sleeping bags but not much better because
furniture the house is important the furniture can come later and so they are
willing to spend much more for the house and take their time with the furniture
and that way the total housing expense may not be more than that 30 odd percent of their income
but it's differently distributed and you see a good deal of this in all areas and these are some
of the things to say about the big outlets and i hope we get into more specifics in the discussion
and I have talked
I think too long
for an introduction and I hope
Sam that you will now turn
it over to our
panelists
What about you? You are the
marketing manager
With anything that's been said
You have tried
What is now
the largest chain
largest company of chain of fashion retail and I won't give you the name was
built by two people who just now retired this year who inherited or took over
what was a miserable small company with one or two mediocre chains of
footwear stores and they built it largely by going to the shopping centers every
Saturday and not going to a shoe store a because they found out that if they go to a shoe store
they immediately again become assistant shoe store managers immediately and see that
here is a brown shoe on the rack that should have only black shoes or you're only lit with
here's a pair where the right shoe is missing it or here is the corner that's dirty and immediately
They had a broom in their hands and were supremely happy doing what they knew how.
They went to every other store.
They behaved what they buy, and this enabled them to anticipate for 30 years to start in the mid-50s.
The shift in American consumer behavior, middle-class buyers of passion-driven goods,
and let's see the one hospital I know that is not suffering today was the one
that where the administrator and his deputy went out fairly early and when
everybody saw the HMOs and so on as enemies and looked at what the customers did
and then realize some of the things that people expect when they get sick or when they leave the hospital.
And I think that is very important.
And one of the first signs that I've seen of a turnaround in the American automobile industry
is that I got the questionnaire in the mail a few weeks ago,
which began by saying
we understand you recently
bought a Toyota
and it came from
the Ford Motor Company and that is
I think the first sign, the first
swallow, it doesn't make a spring yet
but at least it's a sign
that they want to find out
basically who, why
and that's the thing we have never done
in a time of period of
very rapid changes money
Okay, good.